(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
重大告知あり！
Major announcement included!
誕生日3DLIVE やってみたいことやっちゃお！
Birthday 3D LIVE: Let's do everything I want to do!
お待たせ～！
Sorry for the wait!
みんな～、今日が何の日か知ってる～？
Everyone, do you know what day it is today?
うーん、分かるよね！
Hmm, you know, right?
そう！シオンの誕生日～！
That's right! It's Shion's birthday!
今日はなんと...
Today, believe it or not...
でん！
Ta-da!
シオンの、やってみたいことやっちゃお～！
Shion's "Let's do everything I want to do" project!
というわけで、せっかくの誕生日なので、
So, since it's my special birthday,
シオンがめちゃくちゃやりたいことを詰め込む旅に行こうと思います！
I'm going on a trip packed with things I really want to do!
イエーイ！
Yay!
人生初めての体験や毒蛇の...などもあるから、ついてきてね！
There'll be first-time experiences and poisonous snakes... so stay tuned!
じゃあ、出発！
Well then, let's go!
AM 06:00
6:00 AM
東京駅 Tokyo Station
Tokyo Station
おはようございまーす
Good morning!
おはようございまーす...
Good morning...
いやマジで、朝早いよぉ～...
Seriously, it's way too early...
今日はシオンさんが、1日にやりたいことを詰め込んでるんで
Since Shion-san has packed everything she wants to do into today,
行きましょう！
let's get going!
はい！
Okay!
朝ごはんは...
For breakfast...
シオンさんが好きな昆布おにぎりです
I have the kombu onigiri that you like.
ありがとうございます！買ってきてくださって
Thank you so much for buying them for me!
じゃあ...行きましょ！
Well then... let's go!
行きましょう！
Let's go!
しゅっぱ～つ！！
Let's goooo!!
都内から、車に揺られること1時間半。
A one-and-a-half-hour drive from the city.
ナレーション：谷藤 博美
Narrator: Hiromi Tanifuji
シオンのやってみたいことやっちゃお！最初にたどり端いたのは...
Shion's "Doing what I want to do!" The first place we arrived at was...
栃木県 Tochigi Pref.
Tochigi Prefecture
ナレーション：谷藤 博美
Narration: Hiromi Tanifuji
到着
Arrival
はい！というわけで
Yes! So...
やってきました〜！
We've arrived!
ここはどこでしょう！
Where do you think we are?
栃木県で〜す！！
It's Tochigi Prefecture!!
いぇ〜い！！
Yay!!
来ましたね栃木県
We've come to Tochigi Prefecture.
ね〜来ましたね〜
Yeah, we're here.
シオンさん栃木県って来たことありますか？
Shion-san, have you ever been to Tochigi?
いや来たことないですね…
No, I've never been here...
初栃木
Your first time in Tochigi.
はい、初栃木
Yes, first time.
えっ、見える感じ今…
Um, what I can see right now is...
かなり草
A lot of grass.
栃木県はなんかイチゴが美味しいとか
Tochigi is known for delicious strawberries...
はいはいはい
Right, right, right.
宇都宮の餃子とかが有名ですね
And Utsunomiya's gyoza are famous too.
そうなんだ〜！
Is that so~!
まあでも…この辺にはなさそうですけど
Well, but... it doesn't look like there's any around here.
えっちょっと草ですね
It's a bit grassy.
そんな栃木県でシオンさんがやってみたいことは何ですか！？
So, what is it that you want to do here in Tochigi, Shion-san!?
スカイダイビングで〜す！！
Skydiving!!
最初の「やってみたいことやっちゃお」は、スカイダイビング。
The first "Let's do what I want to do" is skydiving.
ご協力いただいたのは、スカイダイブ藤岡さん。
We were assisted by Skydive Fujioka.
飛行機に乗って登っていくのは、
Climbing up in the plane...
こんなに高いところ。
to such a high place.
大丈夫？
Will she be okay?
なんでスカイダイビングなんですか？
Why skydiving?
遊園地のジェットコースターとかめっちゃ好きなんですよ
I really like roller coasters at amusement parks.
おお〜
Ohh~
ってことは高ければ高いほど楽しいかなって思って
So I thought, the higher it is, the more fun it'll be.
いや、一番高そうじゃないですかスカイダイビングが
I mean, skydiving seems to be the highest of all.
そうですね
That's true.
どのくらいの高さだと思います？
How high do you think it is?
えぇ〜！
Ehh~!
ちょっとホントにわかんないなあ…
I really don't know...
シオンさん身長何cmですか？
Shion-san, how tall are you?
145cm
シオンさんが500人いたら…
If there were 500 Shion-sans...
725m
はい。
Yes.
でもスカイツリーって600なんとかメートルですよね？
But the Sky Tree is 600-something meters, right?
そうですね
That's right.
えっいいんじゃないですか！？結構
Wait, isn't that pretty good!?
スカイツリーくらいの高さから飛ぶかな？って感じですか？
You think you'll be jumping from about the height of the Sky Tree?
うん。
Yeah.
スカイツリー1本でいいですか？
Is one Sky Tree enough?
2本！！
Two!!
2本で
Two?
うん。
Yeah.
正解は…
The correct answer is...
スカイツリー
Sky Tree...
6本分の
Six times...
えぇぇ〜！？ｗｗ
Ehhh~!? lolol
3800mです
It's 3800m.
えぇぇ〜！！
Ehhh~!!
シオンさんで言うと、2600シオン
In terms of Shion-sans, that's 2600 Shions.
わかんないなぁ〜ｗｗｗ
I don't even know~ lolol
富士山一個分
Equivalent to one Mount Fuji.
そう言われるとすごいっすね…
When you put it that way, that's incredible...
富士山の上から飛ぶイメージ
Imagine jumping from the top of Mount Fuji.
えぇぇ…
Ehh...
ドキドキしますねぇ…
I'm getting nervous...
ドキドキしてきました？
Are you getting nervous?
うん、してきた。楽しみ！
Yeah, I am. I'm looking forward to it!
じゃあちょっと実際向かってみましょうか
Then, let's head over there.
はい！行きましょう！
Yes! Let's go!
その前に、スカイダイビングを安全に楽しむためのレクチャーを受けないとね。
Before that, she needs a lecture on how to enjoy skydiving safely.
空中での正しい姿勢や着地方法をインストラクターさんから学んで、
She learns the correct posture in the air and the landing method from the instructor...
いざ、搭乗開始。
and now, it's time to board.
搭乗開始
Boarding start
やばいやばい…
This is bad, this is bad...
怖いですか？
Are you scared?
えぇ〜…いや、まだ…
Ehh... no, not yet...
この音が怖いですね
The sound is what's scary.
歯医者さんくらい怖い
As scary as the dentist.
飛行機乗るの何回目ですか？
How many times have you been on a plane?
ねぇ、乗ったことないです！
Actually, I've never been on one!
怖いんでシオンさん先飛んでください…
I'm scared, so please jump first, Shion-san...
ヤです
No way.
じゃんけんして決めますか？
Shall we decide with rock-paper-scissors?
ヤです
No way.
いよいよテイクオフ。
Finally, it's takeoff time.
いよいよテイクオフ
Finally, takeoff
うわあああああああ…
Uwaaaaaaaa...
あぁやばい…！！
Ah, this is bad...!!
やばい！！
Bad!!
飛んでんじゃない？
Aren't we flying?
飛んだぁ〜！！
We're flying~!!
やったぁ〜…！！
Yay...!!
大丈夫！？ｗ
Are you okay!? lol
うははｗｗｗ
Uhaha lolol
ダイジョウブだよー
I'm okay.
きっと…
I think...
まだ上がってますよ…？
We're still going up...?
あぁ、まだ上がってる
Ah, we're still going up.
わぁ、雲の中だ…
Wow, we're in the clouds...
ホントだぁ〜！！
You're right~!!
富士山も見えてきた！
Mount Fuji is coming into view!
富士山
Mt. Fuji
シオンさん！？
Shion-san!?
はいッ…はいッ
Yes... yes.
ゴーグル装着指示
Goggles attachment instruction
あぁ、怖くなってきた…
Ah, I'm getting scared...
ホントだ
It's true.
開いた〜！
It opened~!
アッやばいｗｗｗｗ
Ah, this is bad lolol
がんばれ〜ｗ
Good luck~ lol
キャアアアア！！
Kyaaaaa!!
ひゃあばいｗｗｗ
Hyaba-i lolol
がんばれー！
Good luck!
ひゃあああああああ！！
Hyaaaaaaaa!!
ヤバイ！！
Bad!!
待ってェ↑
Wait↑
どうするの…！？
What are we going to do...!?
※イメージ図
*Image for illustrative purposes
地上へ帰還中
Returning to Earth
いやちょっ...
No, wait...
ちょっと言葉にならないｗｗ
I'm a bit speechless lol
死んだかと思ったｗ
I thought I was gonna die lol
一瞬死んだかと思いましたよね？ｗ
For a moment you thought you died, right? lol
思いましたｗ
I did lol
呼吸出来なかったもん
I couldn't even breathe
いやそう！ｗｗ
Yeah, right! lol
出来なかったよね
I couldn't, right?
出来なかったっすよね
You couldn't, could you?
「口開けてたら死ぬんだ」って
"If I open my mouth, I'll die"
「喋んないと…！」と思って
I thought, "I have to talk...!"
喋りたかったんだけど
I wanted to talk, but...
喋れないｗｗｗ
I can't talk lol
どうでした？上からの景色
How was it? The view from above
めっちゃキレイだったけど…
It was really beautiful, but...
ちょっとホントに思ったより余裕がなかった
Honestly, I had less composure than I thought I would
最高でしたね！！
It was the best!!
最高でした！！
怖いと楽しいどっちが上ですか？
Fear or fun, which one's on top?
怖いっすね
Fear is, yeah
やってみたかった事やれて…
Getting to do what I wanted to do...
よかった！！
That's good!!
めっちゃ良かった！
It was so good!
もう一回やりたいですか？
Do you want to do it again?
いや
No
大満足ですよ！！
I'm fully satisfied!!
ホントに良かった！
It was really great!
いやあマジで楽しかった〜！
Man, it was seriously fun~!
さいこー！！
The best~!!
みんなもでも是非ね、もうひとり1回くらいはやってみて欲しいですけどね
But I'd really like everyone to try it at least once, though
ねえ！ねえ！
Right! Right!
思ってないだろｗ
You don't mean that lol
じゃあ次に行きますか！
Well then, shall we move on!
新幹線　押さえてるから急いで〜！！
We've got Shinkansen booked, so hurry up~!!
続いての やってみたかった事やっちゃお
Doing the next thing I wanted to do
大宮駅から新幹線で2時間ちょっと
From Omiya Station, a little over two hours by Shinkansen
ささ… 美味そっ
Sa-sa... Looks delicious.
もう美味しいですもんね。
It's already delicious, isn't it?
どのくらいになったら食べるとか…？
Around when should we eat it...?
食べるだけだったら、もう茹で上がってるからすぐ食べれるけど…
If it's just for eating, it's already boiled, so you can eat it right away, but...
やっぱもうちょっと…
As expected, a bit more...
染みるってことですよね。
It needs to soak in, right?
カニすごい食べてた時期があるみたいな…
It seems there was a period when you ate a lot of crab...
♪着メロ (笑)
♪ Ringtone (Laughter)
美味そっ！
Looks delicious!
ｗｗｗｗ
Hahahaha
「美味そう」じゃない、「美味い」んだよね！
It's not 'looks delicious', it *is* delicious!
そうですよ？ｗ
That's right! lol
♪着メロ (笑)
♪ Ringtone (Laughter)
忙しい！！ 可愛い。
Busy!! So cute.
沸いてきたんじゃないですか？でも。
Hasn't it started boiling? But still.
沸いてます？
Is it boiling?
聞いてください カニに。
Please ask the crab.
カニに…？ｗ 沸いてますか～！？
To the crab...? lol Are you boiling~!?
沸いてますね。 沸いてますね。
It is boiling. Yes, it is.
盛り上がってます。
It's heating up.
大本命 カニ実食
The Main Event: Tasting the Crab
いただきます。シオンさんハサミで…
Let's eat. Shion-san, use the scissors...
私これでちょっと… 戦ってみます。
I'll try... fighting with this for a bit.
違うよ絶対。それじゃないよ～ｗ
That's definitely wrong. It's not that~ lol
こうなって… 聞いたことあるんですけどねこれで。
It's like this... I've heard of doing it this way though.
アツアツアツアツアツ… アツアツアツｗｗｗ
Hot hot hot hot hot... Hot hot hot! Hahaha
アッスギィッ！ 熱い…
Too hot!! It's hot...
来たわこれ。絶対勝った！！
It's here. I definitely won!!
マジか。ハサミだったか…
Seriously? So it was the scissors...
ザンネン！ どんまいｗ
Too bad! Don't mind. lol
はっはっはｗ プロだ…
Hahahaha. You're a pro...
「なんかめっちゃキレイに剥けた蟹」 紫咲シオン作
"A crab that was peeled very beautifully" by Murasaki Shion
さすがに勝ったかぁｗ 負けたなぁこれ。
As expected, I won! lol I lost this one.
今からでも切るかぁ… 食べてくださいよシオンさん。
Should I cut it now... Please eat, Shion-san.
今からでも遅くない？ いただきます！！
It's not too late even now? Let's eat!!
う～ま～！！！
So good~!!!
マジで美味い。
Seriously delicious.
絶対これだとわかんないじゃないですか…
You definitely can't tell with this...
ふりかけにするからだよ。
It's because you're making it into sprinkles.
え、でもマジで美味しい。柔らか～い。うん！
Eh, but it's seriously delicious. It's so soft. Yeah!
これだけでも全然美味しい…！
Even just this is totally delicious...!
質が良すぎて一口でも… え、うま！美味しさが詰まってますよ。
The quality is so good even with one bite... Eh, delicious! It's packed with flavor.
ジャンケンしよう。
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
ジャン…ケン…？
Rock... paper...?
これ…なんですか？ これなんだと思います？
This... what is it? What do you think this is?
ふっふっふっふｗ グー… グーだな多分これ。
Hahahaha. Rock... this is probably rock.
最初はグー、ジャンケン…
First is rock, rock-paper...
グー！！ いやパーやん！！
Rock!! Wait, it's paper!!
ｗｗｗｗ いやめっちゃパーやん！
Hahahaha. Wait, it's totally paper!
埋まってるとこめっちゃグーだったんですけど… めっちゃパー… ｗｗｗｗ
The part that was buried was totally rock, but... it's totally paper... Hahaha
一生剥けないんですけど私この…
I'll never be able to peel this...
ねえｗｗもうｗｗｗ ば… 爆発ｗｗ
Hey, seriously! lol Ex... Explosion! lol
カニ経験なさすぎて…ｗ 爆発。爪の中身うま…
I have so little crab experience... lol Explosion. The claw contents are good...
ここ美味。イスの中身…？
This part is delicious. The chair's contents...?
こことか… めっちゃ美味しそうですけどね。
This part... looks really delicious though.
うわ… 飲み物じゃん。食べますよ。
Whoa... It's like a drink. I'll eat it.
うわっ！！
Whoa!!
すごい… 濃厚。めっちゃ美味しい…
Amazing... Rich. It's so delicious...
やっぱこれ飲み物。ここ一番好きかもしれないです。
As I thought, this is a drink. I might like this part the most.
めっちゃビール飲みたくなる味。
A taste that really makes you want to drink beer.
わかんないな～ｗ Sumimasen, wakannai koto itte.
I don't know about that~ lol Sorry for saying something you don't know.
あ～… 美味ぁ… ヤバイですよねこれ！！
Ah~... Delicious... This is crazy, right!!
カニの味がする。温泉卵の白身みたいな食感してる。
It tastes like crab. It has a texture like the white of a soft-boiled egg.
わかりやすいなぁ… え、わかりやすいですよね！
That's very easy to understand. It is easy to understand, right!
カニ味のねｗ カニ味の温泉卵のあのぷるぷるのとこ。
Crab flavored, right! That jiggly part of a crab-flavored soft-boiled egg.
これは富山まで来た甲斐ありますね。 ある。マジである。
This makes coming all the way to Toyama worth it. It does. It really does.
今までで食べたカニの中で一番ですか？ 一番ですね！
Is it the best crab you've ever eaten? It's the best!
爪が美味い、爪が。
The claw is delicious, the claw.
じゃあ… ごちそうさましますか。 はい！
Well... shall we say grace? Yes!
せーの、ごちそうさまでした！
Ready, thank you for the meal!
じゃあ～次行きますか！行きますか！
Well~ shall we go to the next place! Shall we!
暗くなってきたしね！ね、超暗いですよ外も。
It's getting dark too! Yeah, it's really dark outside too.
そうですね。じゃあ行きますか。
That's right. Well, let's go.
気づけば夜の7時。
Before I knew it, it was 7 PM.
やってみたいこと、やっちゃお。
Let's do the things I want to try.
最後に、やってみたいことは…？
The last thing I want to try is...?
は～い！というわけで。
Hello~! And so.
みんなには見えてるのでしょうか。もう真っ暗になってね。
I wonder if you all can see. It's already pitch black.
夜景が見える、きれいな景色になりました。
It's become a beautiful scene with a night view.
もう目の前は海で、すごい波の音が響いておりますが。
The sea is right in front of us, and the sound of the waves is echoing loudly.
朝からスカイダイビングして… カニ小屋で美味しいカニいっぱい食べて。
From skydiving in the morning... to eating lots of delicious crab at the crab shack.
ね、富山県来てね！
Yeah, coming to Toyama prefecture!
富山でなんかまだ思い残す事とか…ないんですかね？
Is there nothing else you'll regret leaving Toyama without doing?
あっ、あるかも…！！ あるかもしんない！！ あるかもしんない！！
Ah, there might be...!! There might be!! There might be!!
海水浴。
Sea bathing.
あ、海水浴ね。この…めっちゃ寒そうな…飛び込んでみたい…？
Ah, sea bathing. Into this... really cold looking... you want to try jumping in...?
じゃなくて！！！ じゃなくて～！
Not that!!! Not that~!
今日はですね、誕生日ということで。
Today, since it's my birthday.
なんと6回目の誕生日だそうです。
Apparently, it's my 6th birthday.
すごい！いや、すごい！！ 本当にいつもみんな本当にありがとうございます！
Amazing! Wow, amazing!! Everyone, thank you so much as always!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
というわけでね
And so,
みんなに感謝の気持ちを込めて
to show my gratitude to everyone...
お願いしま〜す！！
Go ahead!!
うわ、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
えええ〜！！
Eeee~!!
すご…
So cool...
めっちゃ近い！
It's so close!
綺麗。
Beautiful.
めっちゃ真ん前だ！
It's right in front of us!
赤。
Red.
この距離で見ることないですよ！
You never see them from this distance!
めっちゃ近い。
So close.
なんと…花火ですね！
Wow... it's fireworks!
うわすごい、大迫力。
Whoa amazing, so powerful.
今の多分シオンさんのシオンの花をイメージした…
That was probably an image of Shion's flower...
あ、そういうこと？
Oh, is that it?
うわあ！すごい！
Whoa! Amazing!
可愛い。
Cute.
花火ね、見たかったんですよね。
I've always wanted to see fireworks.
何年も見てない。
I haven't seen them for years.
めっちゃ綺麗。
So beautiful.
ハート？
A heart?
ハートだったよね今。
That was a heart, wasn't it?
何あれ？ニコちゃんみたいな。
What's that? Like a smiley face.
シオンさんカラーだ。
It's Shion-san colors.
今紫だったよ！
It was purple just now!
めっちゃ綺麗。紫だ。
So beautiful. It's purple.
うわあ！でか！
Whoa! Huge!
高い！高っ！
High! So high!
時差がすごい。
The time lag is crazy.
ぐる〜っとなったら怖かった。
It was scary when it went 'whoosh'.
フィナーレくめぇ！
Finale-esque!
流れ星みたい。
Like shooting stars.
うわすごお…！
Wow, amazing!
すごかった…
That was amazing...
花火打ち上げることって…ないですよね…ｗ
Launching fireworks... isn't something that normally happens... lol
聞いたことないですよｗ
I've never heard of it. lol
いやちょっと…人生でこんな事あるんだーみたいな
Like, wow... things like this actually happen in life.
ねぇ〜！！
Right?!
うわめっちゃ綺麗だったぁ〜！！
Wow, that was so beautiful!!
めっちゃ良かったですねぇ〜！
It was really great!
みんな、どうだったかな〜！
Everyone, how was it?!
めっちゃ綺麗だったよね？
It was really beautiful, wasn't it?
ファンの方も一緒に楽しんでもらえたんじゃないですかね？
I'm sure the fans enjoyed it along with us.
ね、見れてよかった一緒に。ねぇ
Yeah, I'm glad we could see it together. Right?
どうぞこれからも皆さん、よろしくお願いします！
Please continue to support me, everyone!
以上で！！
And that concludes...
シオンのやってみたいことやっちゃお！でした〜！
...Shion's "Let's Do What I Want to Do!" segment!
ありがと〜！
Thank you~!
Murasaki Shion Birthday LIVE 誕生祭3DLIVE やってみたいことやっちゃお！
Murasaki Shion Birthday LIVE 3D Birthday LIVE: Let's do what I want to do!
さあ、シオンの初ロケ、いかがだったでしょうか！
So, how did you like Shion's first on-site shoot!
この後はもちろん、ライブもやっちゃいます！
Of course, the live performance is coming up next!
引き続き盛り上がっていこう！
Let's keep the energy going!
アナタのアイドル
Your idol
サインはB
The sign is B
（うりゃおい！×8）
(Urya-oi! x8)
B小町（フッフー！）
B-Komachi (Fufu-!)
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
We finally met, I'm so happy
待ち遠しくて足をバッタバタしながら
I was so impatient, kicking my feet
今日楽しみで寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was looking forward to today
（オレモー！）
(Me too!)
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous
1分1秒無駄になんてできない
I can't waste a single minute or second
さあ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin
君も！君も！君も！君も！
You! You! You! You!
お・ま・ち・ど・う・さ・ま！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where "love" gathers
日常はクロークの中
Daily life is in the cloakroom
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損！損！
If you come here, you gotta dance or it's a loss!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if there's an audience or not
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる
I can see you clearly
君のサイリウム
Your glowsticks
今は振っとけば飛ぶような
Right now, it feels like I could fly if I swing them
小さな小さな才能だけど
It's a tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を…
Me...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me...
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you an ultimate response.
はい、せーの！
Yes, one-two!
アナタのアイドル
I'm your idol,
サインはB
and the sign is B.
うりゃおい！
Uryaoi!
B小町！
B-Komachi!
フッフー！
Woo-hoo!
あいつは俺が育てたって
I want you to brag about it
近い将来自慢してほしいよ
in the near future, saying you raised me.
こうしちゃいられない
I can't just stay like this.
君と！
With you!
楽しまなきゃ
I've got to have fun.
引きこもりも人見知りも
Both homebodies and shy people,
普段と違う顔見せてよ
show me a different face than usual.
フワフワ！
Fuwa-fuwa!
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
We're all siblings, how's it going?
なりふり構わずに
Without worrying about appearances.
そう！ そうそうそう！
Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
他人に笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if others laugh at you.
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
I don't care what everyone around is saying.
主張強すぎ
Your glowstick's presence
君のサイリウム
is way too strong.
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me,
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
and even if I feel all alone...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you stay by my side,
怖いものはないよ
then I'm not afraid of anything.
うりゃおい！
Uryaoi!
B小町！ フッフー！
B-Komachi! Woo-hoo!
見てよ見てよ何が始まる
Look, look, something's about to start.
君との物語が
The story of you and me.
あぁなんて素晴らしい景色だ！
Ah, what a wonderful sight!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if there's an audience or not.
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small.
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
I can clearly see your glowstick.
今はふーっと飛ぶような
Right now, it's like a fleeting,
小さな小さな才能だけど
tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you stay by my side,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge reaction.
はい、せーの！
Yes, one-two!
アナタのアイドル
I'm your idol,
サインはB
and the sign is B.
うりゃおい！
Uryaoi!
あーっ！
Ahhhh!
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the whole world.
そういう扱い心得て
Understand that's the treatment I expect,
よね！
okay!
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気が付くこと
Rule #1: Notice when I have a different hairstyle.
その二 ちゃんと靴まで見ること いいね？
Rule #2: Look properly down to my shoes, okay?
その三 私の一言には三つの言葉で返事すること
Rule #3: Reply to my every word with three sentences.
わかったら右手がお留守なのをなんとかして！
If you get it, do something about your empty right hand!
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything.
キミに心から思って欲しいの
I want you to think from the bottom of your heart
かわいいって
that I'm cute.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the whole world.
気が付いて ねえねえ 待たせるなんて論外よ
Notice me, hey hey, making me wait is out of the question.
わたしを誰だと思ってるの？
Who do you think I am?
もう何だか あまいものが食べたい！
Ugh, for some reason, I want to eat something sweet!
いますぐによ！
Right now!
かわいいの間違いでしょ
You must mean 'cute' instead.
文句は許しませんの
I won't allow any complaints.
あのね 私の話ちゃんと聞いてる？ちょっと...
Hey, are you listening to me? Hey...
あ、それとね 白いおうじさん 決まってるでしょ？
Ah, and also, the prince on the white horse... it's decided, right?
迎えに来て
Come pick me up.
わかったら かしずいて手を取って「おひめさま」って
If you understand, kneel down, take my hand, and call me 'Princess'.
別にわがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish or anything.
でもね 少し位叱ってくれたっていいのよ？
But you know, it's okay if you scold me just a little bit.
世界で私だけの王子様
The world's only prince just for me.
気が付いて ほらほら お手てが空いてます
Notice me, look look, my hands are empty.
おててが
My hand is...
空いてます
...empty.
無口で
Silent and
無愛想な 王子様
unsociable prince,
もうどうして
Oh, why?
気がついてよ 早く
Notice me, hurry!
ぜったい
You definitely
キミは
don't
わかってない！
understand!
わかってないわ......
You just don't understand...
いちごの乗ったショートケーキ
Shortcake with a strawberry on top,
こだわりたまごのとろけるプリン
melting pudding made with special eggs,
みんな みんな 我慢します...
I'll endure it all, every bit...
わがままな子だと思わないで
Don't think I'm a selfish girl,
わたしだってやればできるの
I can do it if I try,
あとで後悔するわよ
you'll regret it later!
当然です！だってわたしは
Of course! Because I am
世界で一番おひめさま
the number one princess in the world.
ちゃんと見ててよね ちゃんと
Look at me properly, properly,
どこかに行っちゃうよ？
or I might go somewhere else!
ふいに抱きしめられた 急にそんな「えっ？」
Suddenly you hugged me, so out of the blue, "Huh?"
「轢かれる 危ないよ」そう言ってそっぽ向くキミ
"You'll get run over, it's dangerous," you said, then looked away.
こっちのが危ないわよ
This is much more dangerous!
ねぇ 思い出のカケラに
Hey, if I were to name
名前をつけて保存するなら
these fragments of memories,
「宝物」がぴったりだね
"Treasures" would be just right.
そう ココロの容量が
That's right, we've spent time together
いっぱいになるくらいに過ごしたね
until my heart's capacity was full.
ときめき色の毎日
Every day was colored with excitement.
なじんだ制服と上履き
The familiar uniforms and indoor shoes,
ホワイトボードの落書き
the doodles on the whiteboard,
明日の入り口に
at the entrance to tomorrow,
置いてかなくちゃいけないのかな
must we leave them all behind?
でもね、会えたよ！
But you know, I met you!
すてきな天使に
A wonderful angel.
卒業は終わりじゃない
Graduation isn't the end,
これからも仲間だから
because we'll always be friends.
一緒の写真たち
The photos of us together,
おそろいのキーホルダー
our matching keychains,
いつまでも輝いてる
they'll shine forever.
ずっとその笑顔
For that smile always,
ありがとう
thank you.
ねぇ 桜の木もちょっと
Hey, even the cherry trees
背丈が伸びたみたい
seem to have grown a bit taller.
見えないゆっくりなスピードでも
Even at a slow, invisible speed,
きっとあの空は見てたね
I'm sure that sky was watching us.
何度もつまずいたこと それでも
The many times we stumbled, but even so,
最後まで歩けたこと
we walked until the very end.
ふわり放課後の廊下に
Gently, in the hallway after school,
こぼれた音符の羽根
there are feathers of fallen musical notes.
ふかふか積もるまで
Until they pile up softly,
このままでいられたらいいのにな
I wish we could stay like this.
でもね、ふれたよ！
But you know, I touched it!
愛すべき天使に
My lovable angel.
ただいまって言いたくなる
It makes me want to say "I'm home,"
この場所は変わらないよ
this place will never change.
メールの受信箱
The email inbox,
丸したカレンダー
and the circled dates on the calendar.
とびきりの夢と出会い
Meeting an extraordinary dream,
くれた音楽に
and for the music you gave me,
ありがとう
thank you.
駅のホーム
The station platform,
帰り道
the way home.
駅のホーム 変わらぬ道
The station platform, the road that never changes
離れてても 同じ空見上げて
Even if we're apart, looking up at the same sky
ユニゾンで歌おう
Let's sing in unison
でもね、会えたよ！
But you know, we met!
すてきな天使に
To a wonderful angel
卒業は終わりじゃない
Graduation isn't the end
これからも仲間だから
Because we'll always be friends
大好きって言うなら
If I say "I love you"
大大好きって返すよ
I'll reply with "I love you so much"
忘れ物もうないよね
We haven't forgotten anything, right?
ずっと 永遠に 一緒だよ
We'll be together forever, for eternity
ラストチャンスに
On the last chance
飢えたつま先が 踊り出すまま
As my hungry toes start dancing
駆け抜けたこの夜空
Running through this night sky
並のスタンスじゃ 靡かない
Won't be swayed by an ordinary stance
星は宝石の憧れ
Stars are the jewels of longing
浮かぶ涙と汗は 血の名残り
The floating tears and sweat are the remnants of blood
目の中でしか 泳げなきゃ芝居
If you can only swim in your eyes, it's just an act
だけどステージが 逃がさない
But the stage won't let you escape
いついつまでも 憧れ...
Longing for ever and ever...
I've never seen such a liar.
焦がれているよ
I'm yearning for it
生まれつきだっての底なし
Even if born this way, it's bottomless
This lie is love.
And this lie is a gift to the world.
誰と生きたか 思い出して
Remember who you lived with
わたしが命を 賭けるから
Because I'm betting my life
あげるから
Because I'm giving it to you
あなたは時間を くれたのでしょう？
You gave me your time, didn't you?
あらゆる 望みのすべてを
All of every single wish
叶えたら 果たせたら
If they come true, if they are fulfilled
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you
星に願いをかけて
Make a wish upon a star
戻れないから 大切にするの？
Is it because you can't go back that you cherish it?
始めないなら 高を括れるよ
If you don't start, you can look down on it
楽になる日は まず来ない
The day it gets easier will likely never come
日々のなかに 集まる
Gathering within the days
哀しい光
A sorrowful light
生まれつきだっての底なし
Even if born this way, it's bottomless
This lie is love.
And this lie is a gift to the world.
誰を生きたか 忘れちゃった！
I forgot whose life I was living!
あなたに命が 戻るなら
If life returns to you
届くなら
If it reaches you
わたしはどうなろうと 構わないのに
Even though I wouldn't care what happens to me
どうやらすべては 叶わない
It seems not everything will come true
叶わないならば あなたになりたい
If it won't come true, I want to become you
星は砕け光る
Stars shatter and shine
わたしが命を 賭けるから
Because I'm betting my life
あげるから
Because I'm giving it to you
あなたは時間を くれたのでしょう？
You gave me your time, didn't you?
あらゆる 望みのすべてを
All of every single wish
叶えたら 果たせたら
If they come true, if they are fulfilled
あなたに 会いたい
I want to see you
星に願いをかけて
Make a wish upon a star
さあ星の子たちよ
Come now, children of the stars
よくお眠りなさい
Sleep well
さあ星の子たちよ　よくお眠りなさい
Now, children of the stars, sleep well.
輝きは鈍らない　あなたたちならば
Your radiance will never fade, if it's you.
さあ星の子たちよ　よく狙いなさい
Now, children of the stars, take good aim.
またたきを許さない　あなたたちならば
Blinking isn't allowed, if it's you.
「凍りついた心には太陽を」　そして「僕が君にとってそのポジションを」
"The sun for a frozen heart" and "I'll take that position for you"
そんなだいぶ傲慢な思い込みを　こじらせてたんだよ
I've been aggravating such rather arrogant assumptions,
ごめんね　ごめんね　笑ってやって
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, just laugh it off.
火傷しそうなほどポジティブの　冷たさと残酷さに気付いたんだよ
I noticed the coldness and cruelty of being so positive it burns.
きっと君に渡したいものはもっと　ひんやり熱いもの
Surely, what I want to give you is something even more coolly hot.
綺麗事じゃないけど　綺麗で揺るぎないもの
It's not a mere platitude, but something beautiful and unwavering.
うわべよりも胸の奥の奥を温めるもの
Something that warms the very depths of your heart, more than just the surface.
理想だけはあるけど　心のどこ探しても　まるでみつからないんだよ
I have the ideals, but no matter where I search in my heart, I can't find them at all.
伝えたい　伝わらない　その不条理が今
I want to convey, but it's not getting across; that absurdity is now...
キツく縛り付けるんだよ
...binding me so tightly.
臆病な僕のこの一挙手一投足を
Every single move of my cowardly self.
言葉はまるで雪の結晶
Words are just like snowflakes.
君にプレゼントしたくても
Even if I want to give them to you as a gift...
夢中になればなるほどに　形は崩れ落ちて溶けていって
...the more engrossed I get, the more they lose their shape and melt away,
消えてしまうけど
...and disappear.
でも僕が選ぶ言葉が　そこに託された想いが
But the words I choose, the feelings entrusted to them,
君の胸を震わすのを諦められない
I can't give up on making your heart tremble.
愛してるよりも愛が届くまで
Until a love greater than "I love you" reaches you.
もう少しだけ待ってて
Please wait just a little longer.
薄着でただそばに立ってても　不必要に汗をかいてしまう僕なんかもう
Even if I'm just standing by your side in light clothes, someone like me who breaks into an unnecessary sweat...
どうしたって生温くて君を痛めつけてしまうのだろう
...will surely end up hurting you with my lukewarmness no matter what.
「手のひらが熱いほど心は冷たいんでしょう？」
"The hotter your palms are, the colder your heart is, right?"
冗談でもそんな残酷なこと言わないでよ
Don't say such a cruel thing, even as a joke.
別にいいけど　全人生を賭けても　ちゃんと覆させてよ
It's fine, but let me properly disprove that, even if it takes my whole life.
救いたい　救われたい　このイコールが今
I want to save, I want to be saved; this equality is now...
優しく剥がしていくんだよ
...gently peeling away...
堅い理論武装　プライドの過剰包装を
...the hard theoretical armor, the excessive packaging of pride.
正しさよりも優しさが欲しい
I want kindness more than correctness.
そしてそれを受け取れるのは
And the one who can receive that is...
イルミネーションみたいな不特定多数じゃなくて
...not an unspecified large number like illuminations,
ただ一人　君であってほしい
...but just one person—I want it to be you.
かけた言葉で割れたヒビを直そうとして
Trying to mend the cracks with the words I've spoken,
足しすぎた熱量で引かれてしまったカーテン
...the curtains were drawn because of the excessive heat I added.
そんな失敗作を重ねて重ねて重ねて
Piling up failure after failure after failure,
見つけたいんだいつか　最高の一句を
I want to find it someday—the perfect line.
言葉はまるで雪の結晶
Words are just like snowflakes.
君にプレゼントしたとして
Even if I were to give them to you as a gift,
時間が経ってしまえば大抵　記憶から溢れ落ちて溶けていって
once time passes, they usually overflow from memory and melt away,
消えてしまう
...and disappear.
でも絶えず僕らのストーリーに　添えられた字幕のように
But like the subtitles constantly added to our story,
思い返した時　不意に目をやる時に
when looking back, or when catching a glimpse of them unexpectedly,
君の胸を震わすもの　探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for the thing that makes your heart tremble.
愛してるよりも愛が届くまで
Until a love greater than "I love you" reaches you.
...待ってて
...Wait for me
言葉など何も欲しくないほど
So much that I don't want any words
悲しみに凍てつく夜でも
Even on nights frozen with sadness
勝手に君のそばで
By your side, of my own accord
あれこれと考えてる
I'm thinking of this and that
雪が解けても
Even if the snow melts
残ってる
It remains
色は匂へど
Though colors are fragrant
いつか散りぬるを
They will eventually scatter
さ迷う
Wandering
事さえ
Even that
許せなかった
I couldn't forgive
咲き誇る花はいつか
The blooming flowers will one day
教えてくれた
They taught me
生きるだけでは罪と
That living alone is a sin
離れられない
Cannot be separated
離せはしないと
I won't let go
抱く思いは
The feelings I hold
心を躍らせるばかり
Only make my heart dance
色は匂へど
Though colors are fragrant
いつか散りぬるを
They will eventually scatter
さ迷う
Wandering
暇はない
There's no time
けれど後退り
But taking a step back
甘えるか弱さと
Whether to depend on weakness
甘えられぬ弱さで
Or the weakness of not being able to depend
悪夢が
A nightmare
優しく
Gently
私を弄ぶ
Toys with me
弱さ知るアナタは今
You, who knows weakness, now
許してくれた
Have forgiven me
求める者の欲を
The greed of those who seek
健気に咲いた
That bloomed bravely
刹那の美しさ
Beauty of a moment
それを知るには
To know that
遅すぎたのかもしれない
It might have been too late
色は匂へど
Though colors are fragrant
いつか散りぬるを
They will eventually scatter
アナタの
Into your
すべてに
Everything
幼く委ねたい
I want to naively entrust myself
許せぬ優しさと
Unforgivable kindness and
揺るぐ独占欲は
Wavering possessiveness
秤に
On the scales
かけれぬ
Cannot be placed
我儘な愛
Selfish love
色は匂へど
Though colors are fragrant
すべて散りぬるを
Everything will eventually scatter
短き
In short
記憶に
Memories
溢れる想い
Overflowing feelings
枯れゆく命よ
O life that withers away
儚く強くあれ
Be fleeting and strong
無慈悲で
Ruthless
優しい
And kind
時のように
Just like time
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
最後の一秒まで前を向け
Look forward until the very last second
剥がしてもなぜだか増えていくタグと
Tags that somehow increase even if you peel them off
ランク付けされてく不条理な価値
And unreasonable values that keep being ranked
...で人を嫌わないでと
...and please don't hate people
飛び交う言葉を手で覆い隠した
Hidden from the words flying about by my hands
Oh... Time together
灯火を消す前に
Before the light goes out
Oh... Time together
足元を照らせ
Illuminate our path
ほらここをじっと見つめてみて
Hey, try staring right here
最高の味方が映ってるでしょ
Your best ally is reflected there, isn't it?
それは命の証
That is the proof of life
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
たとえ明日世界が滅んでも
Even if the world were to perish tomorrow
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
最後の一秒まで前を向け
Keep looking forward until the very last second
Hip hip hooray
これから先も
From now on as well
Hip hip hooray
君に幸あれ
May happiness be with you
0から1を産むのは容易くないこと
Creating one from zero is no easy feat
肝心なものは見えないし触れないこと
The most important things are invisible and untouchable
不幸とは幸せだと気づけないこと
Unhappiness is not being able to realize you're happy
毎日が誕生日で命日なこと
Every day is both a birthday and a death anniversary
Oh... Stand up, take action
泥沼を掻き分けて
Ploughing through the mire
Oh... Stand up, take action
蓮の花は咲く
A lotus flower blooms
ほらここに手を重ねてみて
Hey, try placing your hand over here
温もりが伝わってくるでしょう
You can feel the warmth, can't you?
それは命の証
That is the proof of life
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
たとえ綺麗事だとしても構わない
Even if it's just lip service, it doesn't matter
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
この世に産まれてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being born into this world
Hip hip hooray
これから先も
From now on as well
Hip hip hooray
君に幸あれ
May happiness be with you
さあさあ、寄ってらっしゃい見てらっしゃい
Come one, come all! Gather 'round!
ろくでなしでいたらこんな風
If you're a good-for-nothing, it's like this
Like this, like this, yeah
アカペラでいたらこんな風
If it's a cappella, it's like this
Like this, like this, yeah
ゲームでいたらこんな風
If it's a game, it's like this
Like this, like this, yeah
ダンスでいたらこんな風
If it's a dance, it's like this
Da-da-da-da-da-da
よく食べて
Eat well
よく眠って
Sleep well
よく遊んで
Play well
よく学んで
Learn well
よく喋って
Talk well
よく喧嘩して
Fight well
ごく普通の毎日を
Live through an ordinary daily life
泣けなくても
Even if you can't cry
笑えなくても
Even if you can't laugh
歌えなくても
Even if you can't sing
何もなくても
Even if you have nothing
愛せなくても
Even if you can't love
愛されなくても
Even if you aren't loved
それでも生きてほしい
I still want you to live
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
たとえ明日世界が滅んでも
Even if the world were to perish tomorrow
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
最後の一秒まで前を向け
Keep looking forward until the very last second
If you are alive
あの子が振り向くかも
That person might look back
If you are alive
宝くじ当たるかも
You might win the lottery
If you are alive
再び始まるかも
Things might start again
生き抜くためなら
If it's for the sake of survival
棒に振れ
Throw it away
水を差せ
Throw cold water
煙に巻け
Confuse them
油売れ
Idle away
現を抜かせ
Lose yourself
そして来週も
And next week
来月も
Next month
来年も
Next year
来世も
The next life
一緒に祝おう
Let's celebrate together
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
たとえ綺麗事だとしても構わない
Even if it's just lip service, it doesn't matter
Blessing for your birthday
Blessing for your everyday
ここに集えた奇跡にありがとう
Thank you for the miracle of gathering here
Hip hip hooray
これから先も
From now on as well
Hip hip hooray
君に幸あれ
May happiness be with you
Hip hip hooray
これから先も
From now on as well
Hip hip hooray
君に幸あれ
May happiness be with you
はい、というわけでここまで見てくれたみんなありがとう！
Alright, thanks to everyone who's watched this far!
この後もう少しだけ続くし、最後に告知もありますが、
It will continue for a little bit longer, and there's an announcement at the end,
今からみんなお待ちかね、紫咲シオン誕生日記念2023グッズの紹介です！
but now, it's time for what you've all been waiting for: the introduction of Shion Murasaki's Birthday Celebration 2023 goods!
いや、今回もね、めっちゃいいのこだわって作っちゃったので、一つ一つ紹介していきたいと思います。
I've put a lot of care into making some really great things this time too, so I'd like to introduce them one by one.
えー、誕生日記念フルセットはこんな感じです。
So, the Birthday Celebration Full Set looks like this.
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Celebration Full Set
いやもうこれ見ただけでね、「うわこれ気になる！早く早く！」ってね、ちょっと思ってると思うんですけど、
I think just by looking at this, you're probably thinking, "Wow, I'm interested! Hurry up and show me!"
まあゆっくり待ってくださいよ。
But please, just wait a moment.
というわけでまず第一、ふわもふあったかブランケット！
So first off, the Fluffy and Warm Blanket!
ふわもふあったかブランケット
Fluffy and Warm Blanket
もうね、イラストがマジで可愛い。もうね、マジで可愛い。
The illustration is seriously cute. Seriously cute.
服装もね、ちょっとあの部屋着っぽい感じになっておりますね。
The outfit also has a bit of a loungewear feel to it.
ブランケットということで、いや今回、全部生地にこだわっております。
Since it's a blanket, I've been very particular about the fabric for everything this time.
なんとですね、あの...
And you see...
フェルト生地とかではなくて...
It's not like a felt material...
...あの、ちゃんとふわふわしてる、あったかい、ふわふわもふもふした感じの生地になっています。
...but a material that's actually fluffy, warm, and has a soft, fuzzy feel to it.
あの、ちゃんとね、肌触りがね、いい感じになってるので、
The texture feels really nice against the skin,
いや、ぜひこれマジで使ってほしいです。本当にいいので。
so I really want you to use it. It's truly great.
おすすめ！
Highly recommended!
次！
Next!
ぐっすりアイマスク！
The "Sleep Tight Eye Mask"!
やーね、塩っ子になってますね。
See, it's designed like a Shiokko.
これ塩っ子になれますからね、これみんな付けたらね。
You can become a Shiokko if you put this on your eyes.
あの、目にね、顔が塩っ子になれるのでね。
Your face will look like a Shiokko's.
これね、リボンが付いてるんですが、
It has a ribbon on it,
リボンもちゃんと立体感でちょっとぷっくりした感じのね、立体感のあるデザインで、
and it's a 3D design with a slightly puffy, dimensional feel.
あの、目とかは刺繍になっております。めっちゃ可愛いし、
The eyes are embroidered. It's super cute!
あの、ほかほか、ちゃんと付け心地めっちゃいいのにしたので、
It's warm and I made sure it's very comfortable to wear,
あの、ちょっとちゃんとね、目、目にね、あの、痛くない、
so it won't hurt your eyes at all.
ふわっとした感じの質感になっているので、
It has a soft and gentle texture,
これを使って、みんな寝てください。毎晩。
so please use this to sleep every night.
いや、これめっちゃいいよ。
This is really good.
次！
Next!
もちもち塩っ子ぬいぐるみ！
The "Squishy Shiokko Plushie"!
あのね、これがね、本当にね...
You see, this one is truly...
これ抱っこして寝てほしいんだよね、みんなに。
I really want everyone to cuddle this while sleeping.
いや、これ、今回はちょっと、みんなが、あの、ゆっくり安眠できるグッズにしようと思って、
I wanted to make a merch item that would help everyone sleep soundly,
これね、もちもちしてるんだよ。触り心地がめっちゃよくて、
and this is so squishy. It feels amazing to touch.
もちもちしてて、なでれる。なでると、ふかふかしてる。
It's squishy and you can pet it. It's soft when you do.
本当にいい感じなので、
It's really nice,
ぜひこれを抱いて寝てほしいですね、皆様には。
so I hope you'll all sleep while hugging it.
はい。
Yes.
次！え、これはちょっと作りたくて作りました。
Next! Oh, I made this one because I really wanted to.
たくさん喋る！ボイスキーホルダー！
The "Talks a Lot! Voice Keychain"!
なんとね、6種類のボイスが入っていて、
It actually contains six different voice clips!
いや、これはですね、過去の配信でみんなにね、あの、言ってほしいセリフみたいなのを募集した時に来た、
In a past stream, I asked everyone for lines they wanted me to say,
変な、あの、結構変なセリフが多かったんですけど、
and there were quite a few strange requests...
いや、ちゃんとね、みんなの要望にも応えられてると思う。
But I think I managed to meet everyone's expectations.
本当に。え、これ、ぜひ聞いてください。みんなの要望が叶うと思って聞いてください。
Seriously. Please listen to it. Listen knowing your requests have been fulfilled.
はい。取り入れておりますので。
Yes, I've included them.
もうね、デザインもめっちゃ可愛いんですよね。なもり先生が描いてくれたんですけど、
The design is super cute too. Namori-sensei drew it.
押すとね、喋りますので、ぜひ、
It talks when you press it, so please,
カバンとかに付けて、毎朝押してください。
attach it to your bag and press it every morning.
はい、最後に、記念ボイス！
Lastly, the commemorative voice pack!
これは、あの、有料のボイスになっております。全部買った方には付いてきますね。
This is a paid voice pack. It's included for those who buy the full set.
あの、ちゃんと、全部セットにも含まれております。
It's properly included in the full set as well.
シチュエーションボイス、「ねむねむシオンちゃん」ということで、
It's a situation voice called "Sleepy Shion-chan".
これは、あの、あの、お昼寝、テーマがお昼寝になっております。ぜひ聞いてください。
The theme for this one is taking a nap. Please give it a listen.
ちょっと恥ずかしいですけど。
It's a bit embarrassing, though.
ちょっと恥ずかしいですけど、あの、ぜひ気になる人は聞いてください。
I'm a bit shy about it, but please check it out if you're interested.
最後に、フルセット購入特典はこちらです。イラストがね、そう、さっき紹介しそびれちゃったんですけど、
Lastly, here's the full set purchase bonus. Regarding the illustration... oh, I forgot to mention this earlier,
さくらしおり先生の、あの、ちょっとキラキラした可愛いね、今回差分で、
it's a sparkling and cute one by Sakura Shiori-sensei.
フードなしのポストカードになっております。
It's a postcard featuring a version without the hood.
これもめっちゃ可愛いですよね。あの、複製サインと、
This is super cute too. It comes with a foil-stamped signature,
今回限定のメッセージが入っております。複製のね、メッセージが入っております。
and a message exclusive to this occasion. It's a printed message.
届いてからのお楽しみということで、ぜひ、
You'll have to wait until it arrives to see it.
あの、記念セットね、フルセットで買ってもらえたらなと思います。
So, I hope you'll consider getting the full commemorative set.
というわけで、いかがだったでしょうか。個人的にはあの、めちゃくちゃこだわったグッズなので、
So, what did you think? Personally, these are goods I put a lot of heart into,
みんなの手元に渡ったら、とても嬉しいなと思っております。
so I'd be very happy if they reach all of you.
よろしくお願いします。この後も、まだ、もう少しだけ続くのでね、
Thank you. There's still a little bit more to go after this.
最後まで目を離さずに、告知もありますので、よろしくお願いします。
So don't take your eyes off until the end. There are announcements too!
それでは、この後も、楽しんでってね！
Well then, please keep enjoying the rest of the show!
さあご覧あれ 君のシンデレラ
Come and take a look, I'm your Cinderella
今宵も始めよう Shall We Dance?
Let's begin tonight as well, shall we dance?
おとぎ話の主人公 いつも鏡の中で夢見てる
The protagonist of a fairy tale, always dreaming inside the mirror
弱音だらけの私でも 画面の中では強くありたい
Even if I'm full of complaints, I want to be strong inside the screen
だけど 強がり 怖がり 寂しがり 弱虫 言われてばかりで
But I'm just putting up a front, being a coward, lonely, and always called a weakling
思い出す度に震える声
My voice trembles every time I remember
なんて そんなの嘘っぱちだから 信じて 私だけを見て
Wait, all of that was just a lie, so believe in me and look only at me
反撃開始のドレスを着て 魔法解ける前に
Putting on my dress to start the counterattack before the magic breaks
さあご覧あれ 君のシンデレラ
Come and take a look, I'm your Cinderella
ガラスの靴履いて 可愛く映ってますか？
Wearing my glass slippers, do I look cute on camera?
誇らしげに踊ってみせよう
I'll show you my dance with pride
これが私なんだ Shall We Dance?
This is who I am, shall we dance?
「所詮は」だなんて分かったふりして 口から出まかせで
Pretending to understand with words like "after all", just talking nonsense
「ホントは」だなんて 甘過ぎ？軽薄？言いたくないんだって
Is saying "actually" too sweet? Or flippant? I didn't want to say it.
もぉ...
Jeez...
ノイズ無視して 全部笑い飛ばして
Ignore the noise, laugh it all away.
不安脱ぎ捨て 立ち止まるな
Discard your anxieties, don't stop.
そらさないで 強くいさせて
Don't look away, let me be strong.
0時を回っても 逃さずに戦ってるの
Even past midnight, I'm fighting without letting go.
気高く華麗に舞い上がる
Soaring high with nobility and brilliance.
泣いてる暇なんかない
There's no time for crying.
「タラレバ」なんじゃなく
Not "what-ifs,"
「これから」を生きたいの
but I want to live for "from now on."
反撃開始のドレスを着て
Wearing a dress to start the counterattack,
魔法解ける前に
before the magic fades.
さあご覧あれ 君のシンデレラ
Now look, your Cinderella.
ガラスの靴履いて 可愛く映ってますか？
Wearing glass slippers, do I look cute to you?
誇らしげに踊って見せよう
I'll show you my dance with pride.
これが私なんだ
This is who I am.
Shall we dance? Ah...
もっと
More,
Shall we dance?
みんなー、見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thanks for watching!
そして、告知があります。
And I have an announcement.
このあとすぐの21時から、シンデレラ・マジックのMVがプレミア公開されます！
Starting soon at 9:00 PM, the "Cinderella Magic" music video will have its premiere!
本当にこだわって作ったMVなので、
It's an MV we put a lot of work into, so...
本当にイラストもね、何十枚もあって、
There are dozens of illustrations too,
見ていて楽しいMVになっていると思うので、
and I think it's a fun video to watch,
みんなに絶対見てほしいです。約束！
so I definitely want everyone to see it. Promise!
それじゃあ、ちゃんと見てね！バイバーイ！
Well then, make sure to watch it! Bye-bye!
シンデレラ・マジック
配信終了後 21:00〜 プレミア公開！！
Cinderella Magic
Premiere at 21:00 after the stream ends!!